## Jia Hui Chow

## Singapore

- Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/lia-Hui-Chow/9b48bc3491bca6d3

Hello! My name is Jia Hui, and I am an inquisitive individual. I am passionate when I put the entirety of my heart to the task at hand. I build models for Natural Language Processing tasks, and have experience rewriting these models in other languages for production. I have also done projects on networks analysis and MySQL.

## Work Experience

#### **Data Scientist**

Refinitiv

April 2018 to Present

- Curated data with Elasticsearch, trained and optimised Deep learning NER models in different languages. Rewrote model in Scala for production. Models slated for release to surface relevant content on millions of daily news articles.
- Increased F1 score of relation extraction model by 10% with more hand-engineered features. Model will be deployed on a risk intelligence product used by top financial and government organizations
- Contributor to an internal Scala library used for model deployment
- Built and integrated training pipeline to production code with modifications in Java and Python

## **Volunteer Project Assistant**

SUTD Lee Kuan Yew Centre for Innovative Cities September 2014 to May 2017

- Synthesized a road map of technological development up to 2050 from official published sources
- Contributed ideas and insights to a report on the future of work, education and healthcare funded by the National

Research Foundation

• Worked with team of four to distill a research article into an infographic, included in the report

## **Applications Engineer**

National Instruments Singapore (Pte) Ltd October 2015 to March 2016

• Client-facing role handling technical sales and service requests, including sales support visits to public sector

customers

· Lead trainer of LabVIEW training courses for industry engineers from wide variety of backgrounds

## **Applications Engineering Intern**

National Instruments Singapore (Pte) Ltd May 2014 to August 2014

• Partnership with SUTD and NI Singapore to develop lesson demonstration in SUTD's Power Electronics syllabus

- Implementation of accompanying technical project showcased in SUTD Open House and presented to NI staff
- Programmed 8-bit music composer

## **Project Engineer**

Defence Science and Technology Agency April 2016

• Worked as a team of 4 in a departmental-level design thinking exercise, collecting problem statements across all

levels of staff to identify and improve process flows

- Assessed and implemented improvements in process and workflow of onsite system testing
- DSTA Learning Recognition Award for exemplary learning attitude

## Education

## Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical Engineering, Magna Cum Laude

Singapore University of Technology and Design

August 2015

## **Asian Leadership Programme**

**Zhejiang University** 

## Skills

Project Management (2 years), Process Improvement (1 year), Python Programming (2 years), Deep Learning (1 year), Natural Language Processing (1 year), Machine Learning (1 year), Data Analytics (1 year), Scala (1 year), Java (Less than 1 year)

#### Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chowjiahui/

## Certifications/Licenses

## Statement of Accomplistment - SQL

Present

Stanford Online Open Edx (taught by Stanford University faculty)

# Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization

Present

Deeplearning.ai by Andrew Ng, Coursera

## **Neural Networks and Deep Learning**

Present

Deeplearning.ai by Andrew Ng, Coursera

## **Structuring Machine Learning Projects**

Present

Deeplearning.ai by Andrew Ng, Coursera